But, you know, last time you were here, you were in a relationship.
You had a reel that went viral on the show.
And people really loved what you were saying.
And one of the things you said in it was,
until you never experienced a nigga try.
I have never experienced, until being with you,
I have never experienced a nigga try.
That's a never, not one.
Never.
It's true.
And then I experienced a nigga stop trying.
And I know niggas is in the comments right now like,
see, that's why she's single.
And it's like, yeah, that is exactly why I'm single.
Because we live in a society that hasn't caught up to women like me.
As black people, like, we just aren't really taught how to love ourselves.
Like, we don't even know what that looks like a lot of times.
Like, I think so many of us are in that process on a regular basis.
Like, what does that actually mean?
Why can't we support each other and know that you have your strengths
and I have my strengths?
Like, your dick and balls does not give you leadership skills.
The idea that you would trust someone to birth the baby
that you would give everything to
but not to handle your feelings is bonkers.
But it's also like women,
we also need to be very practiced at how to handle feelings.
Baby, I will cry for you tonight.
That's why when people say wild shit to me,
like, Amanda Seale hates black men,
I'm like, check my record.
You know how the politicians be like,
check my voting record.
I'm like, check my money record.